Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22 1870-2017
5583/5
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
49.4 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
55.11 cubic feet
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.
Subjects:
Industrial relations -- United States -- Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- ACF Industries (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your Career With ACF, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees Handbook A Summary of Policies & Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AMF Incorporated Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Orientation Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 1980 Directory of Products, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Performance Objectives and Personal Development Goals of, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Management Manpower Planning and Development Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A.O. Smith. Family Service America. Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ATO Inc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Welcome to ATO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Abraham and Strauss Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The New Entrepreneurs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Rate Yourself as a Retail Executive, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Federated Department Stores, Inc. Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The New Entrepreneurs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The New Entrepreneurs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Jordan Marsh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Jordan Marsh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Jordan Marsh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Rate Yourself as a Retail Executive, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Special Report #35, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    November. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Special Report #36, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    March. Item is in English.
- Accountemps, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: World's Largest Temporary Financial Workforce, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Addiction Research Foundation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employee Related Drug Screening, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Employee Related Drug Screening, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Aerojet General Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Our Companies & Our People, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A Profile, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Adult Education Association, USA handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Journal of Research and Theory, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Vol. 31, No. 1, Fall. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Publications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: You Can Make A Difference, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: A Bridge to the New Decade, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Adult Education: A Gateway to Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Nov. 2-7. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Emerging Issues, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Lifelong Learning: The Adult Years, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- African American Labor Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.1 (1980:January-February). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.2 (1980:March-April). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.3 (1980:May June). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.4 (1980:July-August). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.5 (1980:September-October). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.15:no.6 (1980:November-December). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.16:no.1 (1981:January-February). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.16:no.2 (1981:March-April). Item is in English.
  - Item 15: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.16:no.3 (1981:May-June). Item is in English.
  - Item 19: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.16:no.5 (1981:September-October). Item is in English.
  - Item 20: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.17:no.2 (1982:March-April). Item is in English.
  - Item 21: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.18:no.2 (1983:March-April). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.18:no.4 (1983:July-August). Item is in English.
  - Item 25: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.18:no.5 (1983:September-October). Item is in English.
  - Item 27: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.19:no.1 (1984:January-February). Item is in English.
  - Item 28: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 29: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.19:no.2 (1984:March-April-May). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.20:no.2 (1985:March-April-May). Item is in English.
  - Item 31: AALC Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By African-American Labor Center. v.24:no.5 (1989:). Item is in English.
- Agway Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: This is Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: The Birth of Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The Foundation of Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Educational Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: This is Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: De Witt News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sept/Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: People: for and about the employees of Agway Inc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Oct. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Cooperator, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: To: Agway Managers and Supervisors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: This is Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: De Witt News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    September. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Spur, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    August 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Cooperator, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sept. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Agway, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Air Transport Association of America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: How to Fly, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    January. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The People of the airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: The National aviation Authority (NAA), Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Air transport 1907, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: It's About TimeYour Time!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Air Cargoon the move, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: The People of the Airlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: The Airlines and the Environment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Economics of Air Transport: An Overview, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Wrights to wide-bodies: the first 75 Years, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: ATA Directory of Publications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Alabama State Personnel Dept., Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Handbook For Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Alabama State Jobs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Rules of the State Personnel Board, State of Alabama, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: State of Alabama Employee Guidance Sheet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Alaska Division of Personnel, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Executive Management Training "89", Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Laws of Alaska, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Chapter 97. complaints of Employment Discrimination in State Agencies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Salary Survey Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Professional Development Training Opportunities, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Rater's Guide to Performance Appraisals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Deferred Compensation Enrollemtn Kit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Alaska Division of Personnel, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Alaska Public Employees' Retirement Information Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: group Health Care and Life Insurance Plan Information Booklet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    July 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: State of Alaska Survey Salaries & Benefits, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    December. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Alaska Supplemental Benefits System Information Booklet for State of Alaska Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    February 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: State of Alaska Office of the Governor Administrative Order No. 59, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Bibliographic Series Price List, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: General Government Employees Grievance Form, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Alaska Statutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Title 23. Chapter 40. Article 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Group Health Care and Life Insurance Plan Information Booklet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Group Health Care and Life Insurance Plan Information Booklet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alaska Division of Personnel, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: How To Apply For A Job With The State Of Alaska, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Group Health Care and Life Insurance Plan Information booklet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: State of Alaska Performance Evaluation Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Rater's Guide to Performance Appraisals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: State of Alaska Employment Application, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Office Skills Test Application, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Office Skills Test, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    June. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Annual Affirmative Action Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Personnel Rules, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: State of Alaska Performance Evaluation Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 13: State of Alaska Performance Evaluation Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ALLCOA, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Consolidated Balance Sheet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Issue 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Update, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Issue 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Financial Report - First Quarter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Where's the Future? Alcoa Update 1993 Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Alcoa 1991: Special Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alcohol & Drug Problems Association of N. America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Some Thoughts about Drinking: For Women in the Workplace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Alliance of Railway Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: BenefitsYour hidden Paycheck, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Non-exempt Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Management Review and Personal Development Summary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: What President Reagan Decided!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Alleghany-Ludlum Steel Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Allied Chemical Financial Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: 1980 Management Development Programs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Allied Chemical Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Allied Corporation Strength through Diversification, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    By Edward L. Hennessy Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Benefits of Working With Allied Chemical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Employee Emergency Action Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Welcome to Allied Chemical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Employee Commuting Assistance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Salaried Employees Comprehensive Medical Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Employee Emergency Action Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Performance Review and Developments Planning Guidelines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: Performance Review and Development Planning Guidelines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: long-term disability benefits plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Jan 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: life and accident insurance plans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Omnia, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: a.m., Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Nov 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Performance Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 15: Service Award Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 16: careers with Allied Chemical, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 17: A broad spectrum of businesses and careers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 18: salaried employees pension plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 19: Remarks of Mr. E. L. Hennessy, Jr., Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    May 13. Item is in English.
- Allied Chemical Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Advancing World Technology, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Advancing World Technology, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Allied Signal Inc., Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Allied Shield, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Vol. 17 No. 2 March/April. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Allied Shield, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Vol. 17 No. 3 May/June. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Allied Shield, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Vol. 16 No. 5 November/December. Item is in English.
- Allied Van Lines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Progress Review for Nonexempt Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Progress Review, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Benefits for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Handbook for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: The Firm and its Products, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Allis-Chalmers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Aluminum Company of America House Organs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 80, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: will you like Alcoa?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Material Differences, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Career News, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Career News, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Employment Package for New Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: A brief story of aluminum and Alcoa, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Performance Appraisal System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Human Resources/ Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Career Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Aluminum by Alcoa, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Facts About Alcoa, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Year-End Fact Book, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Annual Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Amerada Hess-House Organs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Scope magazine, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Spring. Item is in English.
- Amerada Hess-Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Business of Amerada Hess, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Scope, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The Business of Amerada Hess, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- American Airlines, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: An Overview of the 1986 Survey for the Employees of American Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: An Opinion Survey for the Employees of American Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Classroom Training Programs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Letter from Chairman, President, CEO, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Regulations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Jul 03. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Regulations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    May 08. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Management Performance Appraisal and Tracking, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Anniversaries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Anniversaries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Results of an opinion Survey for the Managers of American Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Corporate Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Employee Suggestion Form, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Corporate and Administrative Office Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: IDEAAS In Action Program Handbook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: An Opinion Survey for the Employees of American Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Flexible Benefits Your Personal Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Management Performance Appraisal and Tracking, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Remarks by Charles Pasciuto Vice President-Labor Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- A.A. Cont., Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: An Opinion Survey for the Managers of American Airlines, Inc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    March 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: AMR/American Airlines Corporate Facts, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    May. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Regulations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- A.A cont., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- American Arbitration Association - Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: commercial Dispute Resolution Procedures, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Resolving Employment Disputes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Resolving Employment Disputes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: For the Labor-Management Professional, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Dispute Management - Today and Tomorrow, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Annual Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Arbitration Times, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Winter. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Alternative Dispute Resolution, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Management Control of Corporate Litigations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Alternative Dispute Resolution: The Travelers' Experience, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Alternative Dispute Resolution in Action, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: No-fault Update, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: For the Labor-Management Professional, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Advanced Arbitration Advocacy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Study Time, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    July. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Study Time, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    April. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Construction Disputes Conference, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    January 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Press Release, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Drug & Alcohol Problems in the Workplace, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Annual Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- American Association for Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Amployment Agencies Officially Exposed, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- American Association of Retired Persons, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)